Hello everyone, today we are going to see
multiplication of 2 x 2 matrix
how to solve this easily
so AB is given by 2 matrix
so we are going to solve this easily
AB is equal to
we have to see row
2 1
so row is 2 1
so we have to write it in row wise
2 1 2 1
next we have
1 3
1 3 1 3
now check the column
column is on this side
so we have 2 1
we have to write this 2 1 in row wise
so 2 1
add 2 and 2
same like this
add 2 here
add this 1 here
now we have to write this 2 1
so we have to write it in row wise
so add 2 here
add 1 here
next we have to write this 0 3
same like this
add 0 here
add 3 here
next
so this is 2 x 2 matrix
this is 2 x 2 matrix
so Laravel answer is
2 x 2 matrix
so this is 2 x 2 matrix
1 3
2 3 x 1
3 0 9
now we have to write 2 x 2 matrix
so
so this is plus in the middle
this is plus here
so now we have to write answer
5 3
5 9
this is the answer
thank you